{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Air Conditioner Installers","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40073/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40073,"taskName":"Central A/C - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Central Air Conditioning System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Air Conditioner Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":3,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"A/C AC Airconditioning Air conditioner","textMessagingName":"Inst Central A/C","rolloverLongDesc":"This is the most common type of central air conditioning with an evaporator unit near the furnace \u0026 an outdoor condenser unit that blows out hot air.","rolloverShortDesc":"Most common type of AC. Includes replacements.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Central Air Conditioning System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Air Conditioning Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Central Air Conditioner System","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Central A/C Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Central A/C - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Central A/C Project","urlName":"Central-A-C-Install","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Air Conditioning Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"A/C AC Air, conditioner, hvac, cool, conditioning, temperature","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":395,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40073/":{"taskOID":40073,"originalTaskOID":40073,"setID":395,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6904,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200581,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or replace central air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace central air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200584,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install or replace window air conditioning unit","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace window air conditioning unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install or replace ductless mini-split air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace ductless mini-split air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200582,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair or service central air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Repair or service central air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200583,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Repair or service window air conditioning unit","answerDisplayText":"Repair or service window air conditioning unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6904,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200581,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or replace central air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace central air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200584,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install or replace window air conditioning unit","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace window air conditioning unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install or replace ductless mini-split air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace ductless mini-split air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200582,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair or service central air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Repair or service central air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200583,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Repair or service window air conditioning unit","answerDisplayText":"Repair or service window air conditioning unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200581,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or replace central air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace central air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200584,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install or replace window air conditioning unit","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace window air conditioning unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install or replace ductless mini-split air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace ductless mini-split air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200582,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair or service central air conditioning system","answerDisplayText":"Repair or service central air conditioning system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200583,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Repair or service window air conditioning unit","answerDisplayText":"Repair or service window air conditioning unit","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}